{
  "title": "Ge'ez Course Quizzes",
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": "symbol_to_name",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ሀ?",
          "options": [
            "Hä",
            "Lä"
          ],
          "answer": "Hä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ለ?",
          "options": [
            "Lä",
            "Mä"
          ],
          "answer": "Lä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ሐ?",
          "options": [
            "Ḥä",
            "Ṣä"
          ],
          "answer": "Ḥä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: መ?",
          "options": [
            "Mä",
            "Śä"
          ],
          "answer": "Mä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ሠ?",
          "options": [
            "Śä",
            "Ḥä"
          ],
          "answer": "Śä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ረ?",
          "options": [
            "Rä",
            "Mä"
          ],
          "answer": "Rä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ሰ?",
          "options": [
            "Sä",
            "Qä"
          ],
          "answer": "Sä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ሸ?",
          "options": [
            "Šä",
            "T’ä"
          ],
          "answer": "Šä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ቀ?",
          "options": [
            "Qä",
            "Bä"
          ],
          "answer": "Qä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: በ?",
          "options": [
            "Bä",
            "Hä"
          ],
          "answer": "Bä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ጠ?",
          "options": [
            "T’ä",
            "Qä"
          ],
          "answer": "T’ä"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Which Ge'ez letter is this: ፀ?",
          "options": [
            "Ṣä",
            "Sä"
          ],
          "answer": "Ṣä"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "syllable_sound",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "hä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "hu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "hi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "ha"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "he"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "hə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሀ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "ho"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "lä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "lu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "li"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "la"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "le"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "lə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ለ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "lo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "ħä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "ħu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "ħi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "ħa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "ħe"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "ħə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሐ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "ħo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "mä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "mu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "mi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "ma"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "me"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "mə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of መ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "mo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "sä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "su"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "si"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "sa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "se"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "sə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሠ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "so"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "rä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "ru"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "ri"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "ra"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "re"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "rə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ረ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "ro"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "sä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "su"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "si"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "sa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "se"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "sə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሰ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "so"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "ʃä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "ʃu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "ʃi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "ʃa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "ʃe"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "ʃə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ሸ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "ʃo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "qä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "qu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "qi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "qa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "qe"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "qə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ቀ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "qo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "bä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "bu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "bi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "ba"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "be"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "bə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of በ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "bo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "tʼä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "tʼu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "tʼi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "tʼa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "tʼe"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "tʼə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ጠ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "tʼo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 1)?",
          "answer": "sˤä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 2)?",
          "answer": "sˤu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 3)?",
          "answer": "sˤi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 4)?",
          "answer": "sˤa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 5)?",
          "answer": "sˤe"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 6)?",
          "answer": "sˤə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "What is the sound of ፀ (order 7)?",
          "answer": "sˤo"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}